What if I told you
that you could make more money in a single
day than the
entire year before it?
But this method isn't just slept on, it's
underrated, and that method
is doing events.
I'm originally a personal trainer,
and I ran my first fat loss seminar all
the
way back in 2017. But five years later,
I sold out the Hammersmith Apollo and
then the Sydney Opera House.
I started my life doing events for the
very
reason you're probably thinking.
To grow the brand, to get myself-- No.
For free flights. I was thinking,
"How could I get a trip home to see my
family
and get the business to pay for it?" I'm
going to do an event in Bracknell, which
is where the budget gym I used to work at
was. I called them up.
"Can I book an event space?" Then I'm
pretty sure I went onto Eventbrite for the
ticketing, and with 12,000 followers,
I went on sale.
Now, this is not financial advice,
but for any of you listening,
anything that you
can say is exclusively
and wholly for the business,
it's not free, but you can get
your business to pay for it. But
when your business spends money on
essentials,
such as a MacBook Pro,
the government look at the amount of
profit that you made
for the year, and it's reduced,
because some money went towards purchasing
things.
Business expense. I'm like,
that doesn't mean it's free.
But the beautiful thing about any of you
that are in the world of content creation
is that technically, again,
not financial advice, if you
were going to go to
Ibiza and create lots of content,
do a bit of networking,
go to some meetings,
maybe scope out some event spaces for a
seminar that you're running next year,
you could turn around and say, "Look,
I didn't even want to." Had to go
exclusively
and wholly for the business to look at
venues.
So your first event doesn't even have to
make money.